Guide to the Western Pennsylvania Conservancy Records and Photographs, 1885-2006 AIS.1999.13
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Records, 1845-1975; 1932-1975; I.
  - Greater Pittsburgh Parks Assn., 1940-1945 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Loose Documents (Mostly Correspondence), 1932-1944 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Keister Park Dedication, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 11-12)
  - Keister Park (Maps and Photographs), 1962 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Keister Park (Ohiopyle), 1961-1962 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Johnston Tavern ( File 2), Construction (Acquisition See File 1), 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Andrew Kerner, 88 Acres, South of Cherry Springs, Potter County, 1952-1982 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Northwest Mining Exchange Company of Erie, OG Rights, Tioga, 1953-1981 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Paid Bills, Cancelled Checks, Greater Pittsburgh Park Assn., 1940-1956 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Maps anf Land Plots, Undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - State Environmental Information and Land Transfers, 1966-1980 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Seven Springs and Fayette County Land Transfers, 1972-1982 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Crawford County Land Transfers, 1977-1981 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Land Transfer, Snyder Farm Land Transfer, 1977-1979 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Photos and Descriptions of Clearview Farms, Undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Westmoreland County Transfers, Locks Mills Land Transfer, 1979-1981 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Forest County Transfers, 1951-1955 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Warren County Transfers, 1979-1983 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Johnston Tavern Restoration, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Johnston Tavern Restoration, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Wildflower Nature Reserve and Frankel Insurance Correspondence, 1965-1971 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Landscape Architecture Correspondence, 1958-1968 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Planning Notes, 1964-1968 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Financial Statistics and Miscellaneous Park Notes, 1953-1963 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Slippery Rock and Lawrence County Transfers, 1967-1970 (Box 18, Folder 1-11)
  - Clark-Woodward Estate, Westmoreland County, 1960-1962 (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
  - Somerset County Transfers, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad and Laurel Ridge Transfers, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Ohiopyle Deeds and Transfers, 1960-1962 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Fayette County Deeds and Transfers, 1968-1970 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Somerset County Deeds and Transfers, 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 7-9)
  - Laurel Ridge Property Deeds and Transfers, 1965-1968 (Box 19, Folder 10-11)
  - William King Est. Somerset and Fayette County Deeds and Transfers, 1969-1971 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Somerset County Deeds and Transfers, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 13-14)
  - Somerset County Deeds and Transfers, 1967-1969 (Box 20, Folder 1-3)
  - Westmoreland County Deeds and Transfers, 1967-1969 (Box 20, Folder 4-9)
  - Westmoreland County: Donegal and Springfield Twp., 1967 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Fisher and Young Inc. Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Merry Transfer, Venango County, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Venango County Transfers, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Fisher and Young Transfers, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Venango County Transfers, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Fisher and Young Transfers, 1967-1969 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Fisher and Young Deeds, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Venango County Maps and Topographical Information, 1967-1969 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Wildflower Reserve Misc., 1966 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Wildflower Reserve Maps, Correspondence, and Finance, 1964-1967 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Point Park College and Wildflower Reserve Collaboration, 1970-1972 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Wildflower Reserve and Raccoon Creek Park, 1960 1969-1972 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Wildflower Reserve Projects and Ideas, 1961-1969 (Box 21, Folder 13-14)
  - Point Park College and Wildflower Reserve Collaboration, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Wildflower Reserve (WFR) Lectures, 1964-1967 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - WFR Projects, 1962-1968 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Jennings Nature Reserve Projects, 1965-1970 (Box 22, Folder 3-4)
  - Jennings Reserve Memorial, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Jennings Reserve Correspondence, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Projects 70, 1964-1970 (Box 22, Folder 7-8)
  - Wildflower Reserve Nature Guide Application, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Wildflower Reserve Correspondence, 1962-1969 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Project 70, 1962-1964 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania Electric Company, 1961-1963 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Lilian McCahan, 1952-1962 (Box 23, Folder 3-4)
  - Lilian McCahan Correspondence, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Custer Transfer, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Devine Transfer, 1964-1967 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Griffith Transfer, 1967-1968 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Hajnik and Kuzina Transfer, 1965-1968 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Lebzelter and Locher Transfers, 1965-1968 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Bethlehem Steel Transfer, 1966-1968 (Box 23, Folder 11-12)
  - Belle and Giancola Transfer, 1967-1969 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Bowser Transfer, 1967-1968 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Cambria County Transfers, 1964-1967 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania Electric Company Right-of-Way, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Pennsylvania New York Central Transportation Company, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Piney Run Mining Company Transfers, 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Cambria County Transfers, 1964-1969 (Box 24, Folder 5-6)
  - Lower Yoder Twp. Transfers, 1964-1967 (Box 24, Folder 7-8)
  - Laurel Ridge Negotiations, 1964-1967 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Misc. Land Grants and Deed Information, 1964-1970 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Springfield Twp., Fayette County Negotiations, 1963-1967 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Laurel Ridge Property Transfer, 1964-1968 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Cook Forest Association Misc., 1948-1965 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Cook Forest Association Legal Documents, 1952-1965 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Cook Forest Association E.W. Arthur Files, 1945-1948 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Cook Forest Association Dedication, 1951-1954 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Cook Forest Correspondence, 1951-1962 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Cook Forest Association Bank Statements and Cancelled Checks, 1946-1956 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Springfield Twp. Deeds, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Springfield Twp. Deeds, 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Saltlick and Springfield Twp. Deeds, 1966-1968 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Saltlick Twp. Deeds, 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Cook Forest Letters and Legal Items (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Hickory Club Property, 1960-1979 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Wildflower Reserve, 1968-1978 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Raccoon Creek State Park (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Ohiopyle Transfers, 1965-1972 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - T.W. Phillips, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Frankel Insurance, 1972-1976 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Radnor Twp. Appraisals, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Charles S. Passavant III, 1974-1976 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Deeds and Transfers in Tioga and Beaver Counties, 1972-1976 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Misc. Photos and Pamphlets, 1974-1976 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Cucumber Run and Ferncliff Infrastructure, 1968-1991 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Sanitary Water Board, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Ferncliff Transfers, 1968-1970 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Department of Health, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Smithfield Mining Correspondence, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Mining Material, 1962-1965 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Ohiopyle and Stewart Township Correspondence, 1962-1967 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Smithfield Mining Correspondence, 1961-1966 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Strip Mining Articles of Agreement, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Sanitary Water Board, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Mine Drainage Hearing-Smithfield, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - North Central Highlands Regional Material, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Joyce Levine Masters Thesis (Draft), 1977 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Environmental Inventories and Maps: North Central Highlands, 1975-1980 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Joyce Levine Masters Thesis (Final), 1977 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - North Central Counties Demographics, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - North Central Counties Population, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Cowamp: North Central Highlands, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Upper Pine Creek Watershed Protection Plan, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Butler County Deeds and Transfers, 1960-1965 (Box 29, Folder 1-3)
  - Stone House Restoration Project, 1964-1967 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Stone House Historical Project, 1963-1965 (Box 29, Folder 5-6)
  - Crossroads Memorial Park, 1963-1966 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Stone House Memorial Project, 1965-1969 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Stone House, Ralph Griswald Landscape Arcitecture, 1962-1966 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Stone House Memos, Photos, and Events, 1963-1965 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Stone House Correspondence and Legislation, 1962-1968 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Brady Twp. Transfers, 1962-1963 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Stone House Restoration Fund Ledger Book, 1963-1963 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Stone House Fundraising, 1962-1963 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Stone House Brochure, 1962-1964 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Stone House Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Stone House Specifications, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 4-5)
  - Les Miller Reports, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Les Miller Reports, 1963-1965 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Les Miller Fallingwater Report, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Les Miller Stone House Reports and Memos, 1964-1967 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Ralph Miner Fallingwater Report, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Clyde Burnsworth Ohiopyle Reports, 1964-1967 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Earl Houts Jennings Reserve Report, 1966-1967 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Frank Lee Lowden Ferncliff Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Norman Fisher Wildflower Reserve Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - John Lewis Fallingwater Report, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - James Lovell Blazing Star, 1965-1966 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Burnsworth Ohiopyle Reports, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Fallingwater Correspondence, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Jennings Reserve Weekly Reports, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Property Transfer Information on Ohiopyle, 1959-1969 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Tax and Liability information on Ohiopyle and McConnells Mill, 1965-1970 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Ohiopyle Relocation, Redevelopment, and Protests, 1963-1966 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Ohiopyle Road and Electric Development, 1966-1967 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Ohiopyle Cost and Development Analysis, 1958-1968 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Ohiopyle Legal Information, 1965-1967 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Ohiopyle Borough: Politics, Finance, Emergency and Administration, 1963-1967 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Ohiopyle Pictures and Blueprints, Undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Uniontown Railroad, 1963-1967 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Economic Development Administration, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Ohiopyle Properties, 1960-1964 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Ferncliff Park, 1958-1968 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Ferncliff Park, 1963-1964 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Neighboring Community Items, 1965-1969 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Fayette County Development, 1962-1968 (Box 31, Folder 15-16)
  - Ohiopyle, Fayette County Misc., 1960-1964 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Fayette County Zoning and Planning, 1959-1966 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - News articles from Uniontown, 1961-1968 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Articles, and Memorandum, 1961-1968 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Items of Fayette County, 1960-1968 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Items of Fayette County, 1960-1968 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - West Penn Power, 1959-1965 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Fayette and Westmoreland County Deeds and Transfers, 1960-1966 (Box 32, Folder 7-13)
  - Fayette and Westmoreland County Deeds and Transfer to Mrs. Ruth Burdman, 1961-1962 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Fayette and Westmoreland County Deeds and Transfers, 1961-1963 (Box 33, Folder 1-10)
  - Keister Park and Thorpe Knob, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Fayette Deeds and Transfers, 1961-1963 (Box 34, Folder 1-5)
  - Johnstown Tavern, 1965-1967 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Ohiopyle Sewer and Water Project, 1966-1967 (Box 34, Folder 7-9)
  - Chester Engineers-Ohiopyle Project, 1964-1967 (Box 34, Folder 10-11)
  - Chester Engineers-Ohiopyle Project, 1964-1967 (Box 34, Folder 12-13)
  - Federal Funds, 1960-1964 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Ohiopyle Zoning, 1964-1965 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - William H. Pugsley, 1960-1965, 1965-1977 (Box 35, Folder 2-5)
  - Ohiopyle Property Notes, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Ohiopyle Property Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 35, Folder 7-8)
  - Ohiopyle Memos, 1960-1965 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Ohiopyle House Projects, 1960-1965 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Ohiopyle Hotel Improvements, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Deeds to the Western Maryland Railroad, Undated (Box 36, Folder 1-6)
  - WPC Land Conveyances, 1975-1980 (Box 36, Folder 7-8)
  - National Park Service Documents, 1974-1980 (Box 37, Folder 1-2)
  - Deeds in Forest County, 1976-1978 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Warren County Deeds, 1977-1980 (Box 37, Folder 4-6)
  - Hopkins Deed, Forest County, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Warren and Erie County Deeds, 1977-1978 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Esther Williams Allegheny River Deed, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Forest County Deeds and NPS Guide, 1978-1980 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Forest County Deeds and Tract Information, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Ohiopyle Borough Dinner (Water System Opening), Sept 10, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Ohiopyle, Dinner, Sept 1, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Ohiopyle, Economy League (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Western Maryland Railroad Trip, May 21, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Western Maryland Railroad Trip, Nov 30, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Projects, Ohiopyle Railroads (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Johnston Tavern Dedication, May 18, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 7-15)
  - Ohiopyle Sewerage Project (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Ohiopyle House/Fire (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Acquisition Clips (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Ohiopyle State Park, Acquisitions, Transfers, May 1963 (Box 38, Folder 19-20)
  - Ohiopyle Clippings (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Ohiopyle Story (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Ohiopyle Redevelopment, Dec 1963 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Ferncliff, Current Projects: General List (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Ferncliff, Current Projects: Lee Lowden, Animal and Bird Checklists (Box 38, Folder 25-26)
  - Ferncliff, Current Projects: Fairbanks-Horix Overlook (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Ferncliff, Current Projects: McCormick Overlook (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Ferncliff, Current Projects: HMitchell House (Miller Reports) (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Ferncliff, Current Projects: Natural Landmark (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Ferncliff, Current Projects: Plant List, Cucumber Run (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Ferncliff, Current Projects: M.S. Norris Engineering (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Ferncliff, Current Projects: Transfer to Commonwealth of PA (Box 38, Folder 33)
- Photographs, 1885-2006; 1950-2004; II.
  The photograph collection depicts the work of the WPC to conserve and protect Western Pennsylvania's natural resources. The collection contains both black and white and color prints of various sizes, 35mm slides, negatives, glass plate negatives, and lantern slides.
  The images in this collection have been separated into three series: Land and Water, Community Garden Program, and Personnel and Related Activities.
  The vast majority of images in the Land and Water series date between the early 1950s and the late 1970s. McConnell's Mill, Ohiopyle, and Raccoon Creek State Parks are prominently featured in this series, along with Fallingwater and the restoration of Johnston Tavern, the Old Stone House, and the Burke Building.
  The Community Garden Program has allowed the WPC to partner with local communities to plant and maintain 135 gardens in 20 counties throughout Western Pennsylvania. The images in this series date between the early 1980s and the early 2000s. The earlier images are mostly color prints, negatives and polaroids of community gardens, parklets, the Pittsburgh Park and Playground Program, and high rise floral beds. Later images include color prints, negatives, slides, and CDs. Not only do these images depict the same content as earlier years, they also document the vast growth of the Community Garden Program. Roadways, tunnels, bridges, and schools are a prominent feature of this series.
  Personnel and Related Activities include images relating directly to WPC staff and WPC members. The images in this series date between the early 1950s and early 2000s.
  - Land and Water, 1885-1975; 1950-1975; 1.
    This subseries contains B/W prints of various sizes, negatives, 35mm slides, 5x7 glass plate negatives, and 3x4 lantern slides depicting land which the Western Pennsylvania Conservancy has worked to transform into some of today's most utilized parks, nature reserves, protected state game lands, and historical sites in Western Pennsylvania. Prominent geographic locations of note in this collection include: Ohiopyle State Park; McConnell's Mill State Park; Raccoon Creek State Park, with a focus on the Wildflower Reserve; Cook Forest; Ferncliff Peninsula; Jennings Nature Reserve and Blazing Star Prairie; Laurel Ridge; McCoy Farm; Conneaut Marsh; Fallingwater; the Old Stone House; the Johnston Tavern; and the Burke Building. Beyond geographic locations, this subseries contains general images, including: scenic views; rivers and streams; flowers and forests; and wildlife.
    Prominent photographers in this subseries include Galen W. Barton, Michael Fedison, Norman Fisher, Peggy Fisher, Thomas Jarrett, James McClain, Leslie Miller, Graham M. Netting, Thomas C. Pears, Joseph B. White, and Paul G. Wiegman. The majority of these images are marked with dates and locations, while others have been marked up for publication. Other photographs were taken by staff photographers for the following newspapers: The Daily News, The Evening Standard, The Pittsburgh Press, The Youngstown Vindicator, Valley Daily News, and the Pittsburgh Post-Gazette. Photographs in the Pittsburgh folder contain shots taken by Harold Corsini.
    - Aerial Views, Caves, Slides (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Allegheny River Islands, Slides (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Bear Run, Prints and Negatives (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Bear Run, Slides (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Beechwood Farms Nature Reserve, Prints (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Breakneck Bridge, Prints and Negatives (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Buchanan Run, Prints (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Burke Building, Prints, Negatives, and Slides (Box 39, Folder 8)
      The Burke Building is the oldest commercial building in downtown Pittsburgh, erected in 1836. Before the WPC purchased the building in 1996, it served as a restaurant. Picutres of the restaurant, taken about 1970, are included in this folder.
    - Burke Building Renovation, Slides (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Burke Building Renovation, March 26, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Burke Building Renovation, April 4, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Burke Building Renovation, April 9, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Burke Building Renovation, April 16, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Burke Building Renovation, April 23, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Burke Building Renovation, April 30, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Burke Building Renovation, June 4, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Burke Building Renovation, July 1996; Prints (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Burke Building Renovation, July 29, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Burke Building Renovation, August 1996; Prints (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Burke Building Renovation, August 16, 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Burke Building Renovation, September 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Burke Building Renovation, October 1996; Prints and Negatives (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Burke Building Renovation, October 1996; Prints (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Burke Building Renovation, November 1996; Prints (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Burke Building Renovation, December 1996; Prints (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Burke Building Renovation, January 1997; Prints and Negatives (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Burke Building Renovation, Prints (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Burke Building Renovation, Prints (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Burke Building Renovation, Prints (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Burke Building Renovation, Prints (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - Burke Building Renovation, Prints and Negatives (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Burke Building Renovation, Prints and Negatives (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Butler County, Route 528 Land Acquisitions, Prints (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Catherine Swamp, Prints (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Charles F. Chubb Memorial Fountain, Prints and Negatives (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Cherry Run, Prints (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Cherry Run, Slides (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Children, Scenic, Wildlife, Between 1965 and 1966; Negatives (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Children, Scenic, Wildlife, Between 1967 and 1968; Negatives (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Children, Scenic, Wildlife, Between 1969 and 1970; Negatives (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Clarion River, Prints and Negatives (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Clarion River, Slides (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Columbus Bog, Prints and Slides (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Conemaugh Gorge, Prints and Negatives (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Confluence, Pennsylvania, Prints (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Conneaut Marsh, Prints (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Conneaut Marsh, Slides (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Cook Forest State Park, Prints and Negatives (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Cook Forest State Park, Prints and Negatives (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Cook Forest State Park, Slides (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Copied Charts and Maps, Negatives (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Cucumber Falls, Prints (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - David Roderick Wildlife Reserve, Prints (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Enlow Fork, Prints (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Erie National Wildlife Refuge, Prints (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Fallingwater, Prints and Negatives (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Fallingwater, Slides (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Farmland, Flowers, Slides (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Ferncliff Peninsula Natural Area, Prints and Negatives (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Flowers, Prints and Negatives (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Foliage, Forests, Slides (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Forests, Prints and Negatives (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - Fort Necessity, Prints (Box 40, Folder 33)
    - Fox Estate, Foxburg, Pennsylvania, Prints (Box 40, Folder 34)
    - French Creek, Slides (Box 40, Folder 35)
    - Fringed Gentian, Prints (Box 40, Folder 36)
    - Fringed Gentian, Slides (Box 40, Folder 37)
    - Greene County, Prints (Box 40, Folder 38)
    - Harmon Creek Coal Company, Property, Prints (Box 40, Folder 39)
    - Hetzel Studio, Prints (Box 40, Folder 40)
    - Hickory Creek, Prints (Box 40, Folder 41)
    - Hosterman's Pit, Prints (Box 40, Folder 42)
    - Indian Creek Rail Road, Prints and Negatives (Box 40, Folder 43)
    - Jennings Nature Reserve and Blazing Star Prairie, Prints and Negatives (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Jennings Nature Reserve and Blazing Star Prairie, Prints and Negatives (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Jennings Nature Reserve: A Collection of Photographs, Prints and Negatives (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Johnston Tavern, Prints and Negatives (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Johnston Tavern Dedication, Prints (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Johnston Tavern Restoration, Prints (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Jonathan Run, Prints (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Keister Park, Prints (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Lake Arthur, Prints (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Lake Arthur Dam Groundbreaking and Dedication, Prints (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Lake Pleasant Properties of Conservation Interest, Prints (Box 41, Folder 11)